http://www.ilrg.com/terms/privacy.html

Wyoming
you are here:
forms menu
our privacy policy
you are here:
forms menu
our privacy policy -
you are here:
forms menu
our privacy policy - publiclegal
Our Privacy PolicyLast Updated: August 7, 2019NOTICE: Click here for important information about safe internet browsing from the Federal Trade Commission.Maximilian Ventures LLC, a Delaware limited liability company doing business as "PublicLegal" and "PublicLegalForms.com", owns and operates the Internet Legal Research Group website, www.ilrg.com (hereafter, the "Site" or "ILRG.com"). Maximilian Ventures LLC promotes trust, privacy and security as core attributes of our service to our user. Maximilian Ventures LLC has adopted this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to communicate clearly our firm commitment to your privacy. It is this respect for user privacy that is a fundamental component to our mission. Using our website demonstrates your consent to Maximilian Ventures LLC's collection and use of information pursuant to this Policy, and continued use of this site following the posting of changes to this Policy will signify your acceptance of such changes. This Policy governs the use of your name, e-mail address, payment information, and similar personal information that you may provide us in the course of using our website, products or services.If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.Information Collection and Use. Maximilian Ventures LLC collects personal information to provide certain products and services to our customers. For example, if you:Place a product or service order, Maximilian Ventures LLC or one of our contracted third-party payment processing partners (Apple, Amazon, PayPal, or Stripe) will receive your name, e-mail address, and credit card information only to fulfill your order and charge you for the product or service you have ordered. We or our partner encrypts your information using industry-leading encryption technology. We do not retain or store credit your card information, except for the last four digits of your credit card number, which we retain only for the purpose of authenticating you in case you contact us later for help or support with your order.Post information on any of our interactive areas, Maximilian Ventures LLC will collect information from you in order to e-mail you major updates about Internet Legal Research Group, the products and services; andSign-up for the Internet Legal Research Group mailing list, Maximilian Ventures LLC will collect information from you to facilitate the publishing of that mailing list.Information that you submit about yourself may be used by Maximilian Ventures LLC to provide you requested services, communicate with you about our products, improve your online experience, or support our continuing efforts to offer you the information and services you want most. We do not share personal information about you with non-affiliated companies or organizations outside of Maximilian Ventures LLC without your explicit permission. Maximilian Ventures LLC does, however, provide aggregate statistics and information about our sales, traffic patterns and related site information to third parties.We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.In certain situations, Maximilian Ventures LLC may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, or similar legal process, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. If Maximilian Ventures LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.Confidentiality and Security. Maximilian Ventures LLC limits access to personal information about you to employees and contractors who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Maximilian Ventures LLC has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. In addition, as a condition of employment or business partnership, Maximilian Ventures LLC requires all its employees and contractors to sign confidentiality contracts. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us by emailing webmaster03@ilrg.com.Annual Certification of Responsible Data Collection and Processing Practices. To help ensure purchasing from us is safe, Maximilian Ventures LLC undertakes extraordinary efforts to adopt and to maintain policies, practices, and procedures consistent with regulatory expectations and external standards for privacy accountability. We place the highest priority on safeguarding the personally identifiable information of our customers and all other highly sensitive information, such as your credit card details. Our privacy and data governance practices are certified annually by a neutral, external, and independent third party.Safety and Security of Our Payment Processing Partners. When you purchase a product or service through our website, you can choose from among several different payment options offered by third-party payment processors, to complete the transaction. Read why purchasing from us using each of these payment options is a safe experience: Apple Pay, Amazon Pay, PayPal, and Stripe (our processor partner for credit card payments including American Express, Visa, MasterCard, and Discover). These companies do not retain, share, store or use personal information for any secondary purposes.Maximilian Ventures LLC's Security is Certified Daily by an Independent Third Party. Maximilian Ventures LLC has contracted with McAfee, a wholly owned subsidiary of Intel Corporation (NASDAQ: INTC). McAfee is the leading provider of Internet security auditing services. McAfee provides independent daily monitoring, testing, and certification of Maximilian Ventures LLC's web site and e-commerce security. Maximilian Ventures LLC is tested and certified daily to pass the FBI/SANS Internet Security Test. The "live" McAfee® Secure mark, shown on the right, appears only when a web site's security meets the highest security scanning standards of the U.S. government, Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Discover, and JCB. The daily scanning and certification show that Maximilian Ventures LLC meets all payment card industry guidelines for remote web server vulnerability testing to help protect customer personal information from hackers. McAfee SECURE sites help keep you safe from identity theft, credit card fraud, spyware, spam, viruses and online scams.Security with DigiCert® and Extended Validation SSL. Maximilian Ventures LLC has contracted with DigiCert, Inc., the premier provider of high-assurance digital certificates. With DigiCert, you are assured that you have secure communications with Maximilian Ventures LLC and not another site. Maximilian Ventures LLC uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer), the industry standard method for computers to communicate securely without risk of manipulation or recipient impersonation. Maximilian Ventures LLC utilizes this encryption during the online checkout process, including the acceptance of your credit card information, and the management of your account. The "Norton Secured" DigiCert mark, shown on the right, is only authorized for display when a business has passed DigiCert's rigorous identity authentication process and has been certified as a valid and trusted business. In addition, we have applied for and received from DigiCert an Extended Validation (EV) SSL certificate, the highest degree of authentication available. The EV process requires more evaluation and documentation checks for applicants than those associated with other types of certificates. DigiCert has outlined the criteria that its applicants must meet to receive an EV SSL certificate.E-mail Communications. Maximilian Ventures LLC will send replies to customer e-mail via e-mail. If you have sent a request to Maximilian Ventures LLC about which we need to communicate with you, we may do so by e-mail or telephone, if you provided your telephone number to us.Updating Your Information. Upon request Maximilian Ventures LLC will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. As a customer of Maximilian Ventures LLC, you may alter or delete your information at any time. Maximilian Ventures LLC offers the following options for changing and modifying your information.You may send an email to webmaster03@ilrg.com.You may send mail to Maximilian Ventures LLC at the following postal address: 251 Little Falls Drive, Ste. 5800, Wilmington, Delaware 19808 USAYou may call us at: +1 (800) 987-9087, ext. 2You may fax us at +1 (302) 416-5565We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.Anti-Spam Policy. Maximilian Ventures LLC is 100% opposed to unsolicited commercial email ("spam"). Maximilian Ventures LLC does not send emails to anyone without permission and does not sell or provide email addresses to any unauthorized third party. If you receive any unsolicited emails from spammers, please be assured that Maximilian Ventures LLC did not provide your email address to such parties.Log Files. As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.Maximilian Ventures LLC and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.Interactive Areas. Maximilian Ventures LLC is not liable for information posted in interactive areas. Maximilian Ventures LLC provides interactive areas such as polling forums to enhance the user experience and to build a healthy community around our website's products and services. You acknowledge that should you participate in such interactive areas, the information you voluntarily post about yourself and third parties in such areas might be accessed, collected and used by third parties outside of the Site. In addition, you may not post any defamatory, obscene, slanderous, or otherwise illegal material, or any material which infringes any third-party copyrights or other intellectual property rights on any interactive areas. Violators will be subject to termination of accounts and possible legal action. Although Maximilian Ventures LLC employs advanced security technology, it cannot guarantee complete security in personal websites or password-protected areas, and Maximilian Ventures LLC will not be held liable for any user's or other visitor's disclosure of personal information on the Site or any other website operated by Maximilian Ventures LLC. If you are under 18 years of age, you should ask your parents permission before posting any personal information on the Internet, such as your name, address, age, or e-mail address.Data Retention. We are committed to following the highest standards and best practices within the industry for privacy and security as it relates to data retention. Consistent with those standards, under no circumstances do we ever retain or store your credit card information. The only exception is that we will retain only the last four digits of your credit card number, which, as noted above, we will retain only for the purpose of authenticating you in case you contact us later for help or support. We will retain your information (such as name and/or email address) for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, email us at webmaster03@ilrg.com, or call us on +1 (800) 987-9087, ext. 2, or contact us by one of the other methods noted above. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.Links to External Sites. Maximilian Ventures LLC contains thousands of links to websites not owned or controlled by Maximilian Ventures LLC. Maximilian Ventures LLC is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any such sites. Our Privacy Policy is a component of, and incorporated into, our Terms and Conditions of Use. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Maximilian Ventures LLC.Surveys and Contests. From time-to-time Maximilian Ventures LLC requests information from our visitors via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is voluntary, and the visitor therefore has a choice whether to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and mailing address, as well as demographic information (such as zip code or age). Contact information is used to notify the winners and to award prizes. Survey information is used for purposes improving the use and satisfaction of this site, as well as the relevance of our product offerings and content.Notification of Changes. Maximilian Ventures LLC will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. If we make any material changes in our privacy practices, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users prior to the change becoming effective. In some cases where we post the notice, we also email users, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. You are responsible for checking this policy periodically to monitor any changes to our privacy practices. Maximilian Ventures LLC reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time.A Special Note about Children. Children are not eligible to use our services, and Maximilian Ventures LLC asks that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to Maximilian Ventures LLC. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians.Contacting the Web Site. If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: Maximilian Ventures LLC, 251 Little Falls Drive, Ste. 5800, Wilmington, Delaware 19808, United States of America; +1 (800) 987-9087 or +1 (302) 416-5565 (fax); or webmaster03@ilrg.com.
